Everyone, all of you friends are welcome.
In this video, we are going to see
how the Day 2 status of ICICI Prudential AMC IPO
looks after the end of Day 2.  Is there any opportunity emerging here for retailers
and if we talk about this IPO, then the
rise in the grey market premium, is it sustaining
or not, we are going to
talk about it in detail in this video.
So watch the video till the end and subscribe to the channel for such
daily updates related to IPO grey market premium.
Also, the link of the Twitter group is given in the comments.  You
can also join there
for timely updates.  Talking about the first of all
ICICI Prudential AMC IPO, the
deadline for applying for this IPO was
12th of December, the first day of application,
which has already ended here.
Talking about today, the
second day for applying here was 15th of December,
that too has
ended and tomorrow is the last
day when you will get the opportunity to apply for this IPO.
If we talk about this IPO till now, then
how many IPOs have been subscribed till two days
and what are the chances of getting some allotment
in which category,
we will discuss it further but
if you apply in this IPO and
get allotment then here
shares with face value of ₹1 are ₹2165, those who will
select six equity shares at the current price of ₹2165 while applying,
they will be seen getting allotment in this IPO, the
company's offer is for sale, completely
whatever money the company is raising from the market is
seen going to the promoters of the company and the existing share holders category.  If we talk about the issue size of the company here, then the
issue size is approximately Rs 10,600 crore.  Out of which
5% has been reserved for the share holders category.
After that, if we talk,
50% shares will be allocated to QIB.
In which we can also see anchor investors
coming.  35% shares will be allocated
to NI category, 10% shares will be allocated to
retailers category and 15% shares will be
allocated to NI category.  Well, if we
talk about the important dates of this company in the coming time, then 16th of
December is the closing date of this IPO.  On
17th of December, you will get information about whether
you got allotment in this IPO or not.  The
date for refunding the money if not received is 18th of December.  The
date for crediting the shares to the demat account is 18th of December.
And on 19th of December it will be seen happening on BSN 2G.
Well, if we look at this company, then
how much amount is
required here to apply for a minimum of one lot, then approximately ₹12,990 amount is required here to
apply for a minimum of one lot in this IPO.
Talking about Small NI HAI, the
requirement here is around ₹2,7840.  Talking about Big HI NI, the
requirement here is around ₹1,230.
If we talk about the company, then
before the opening of this IPO on 11th
December, then on 11th
December itself, out of its total issue size, there
is 1 crore 39573 equity.  Shares worth up to ₹321 crore have been
allocated to you, the anchor investor.  The
opportunity to sell 50% of the shares allocated in this manner will be available after 30 days, i.e. on
16th of January. The opportunity to sell the remaining 50%
shares will be available on
17th of March.  Date is going to be important
for you in the coming times.
If we look at the company,
here in the anchor investor
book list of this company,
you will see many big names here,
if we look at it, the name of Life Insurance
Corporation of India LIC can also be seen
added here.  Let's talk about Capital Group
or let's talk about the Government of
Singapore.  You can also see his participation here as an
anchor investor.
And
talk about the Authority of Singapore.  Their
participation is visible here
and through different schemes of HDFC Mutual Fund, you can
see a lot of participation here, let us talk about their scheme SBI
Mutual Funds.
Their participation is visible here.
Talking about fidelity, their participation
is visible here.  Also, if we
talk about JP Morgan.  So participation
in this IPO is visible here through three schemes.  Whether you
talk about JF India or the government pension funds that have gone
global, you can
see them participating in this IPO.
Participation of India Mutual Fund is visible in this IPO.
Through different schemes,
different schemes of Kotak Mahindra Mutual Fund are
seen participating here.  Abu Dhabi investment
funds have participation here.
Talk about BlackRock, talk about Goldman size.
Their participation
is visible here in the anchor investor,
if you analyze the anchor investor book list of this company properly, then the
anchor investor book
list of this company is seen to be quite strong here.   Out of which
Global Research Equity Extent,
which is the master funds, has
participation here.  Participation of Aditya Birla Sun Life
Mutual Funds
is visible here.  Here the participation of MI Asset Mutual Fund is
visible in this company.
Along with this, the participation of HDFC NPS Trust
is visible here through different schemes.
Talking about UTI NPS, they have
participation here.  Along with this, the participation of DSP mutual fund of this company is
visible here.  If we talk about
Franklin India Large Cap
Funds, its name is visible here.  And
CRAs which are RECO small cap funds are seen
participating here through the scheme.
If we talk about the anchor investor book list, then
another big name here is HSBC Global
Investment Fund India Equity,
their participation
is visible here.  If we talk about the schemes here, then the
total participation of anchor
investors through different schemes
in this IPO is visible, then
through approximately 149 schemes,
in this IPO, a
total of 1 crore 39573
equity shares worth Rs 3221 crore were allotted to the anchor investors.  Let's
talk about the response to this IPO so far.  So
you can see the responses so far.  The subscription figures for the IPO show us the subscription figures for the
QIB category on the first
day up to 1.97% after the close of the second day.
By 2.22 pm after the end of the second day, the
IPO QIB category had received bids worth approximately Rs
crore.  The
response seen from QIBs in this IPO on the first day is
not the same as the continued response on the second day.  But here in
this type of big issue, you
people are seeing such a
positive response on the first day in this IPO.
But the IPO which was
subscribed 0.38 times on the first day from the NI category, has been
subscribed 3.77 times after the end of the second day.
Which is a very good response.  The
first day participation of QIB
is visible.  That is why you are seeing IPOs in the NI category getting
subscribed almost four times.
Due to bidding up to Rs 5696 crore, the IPO is seen getting subscribed more than three times here.
APO is subscribed 3.79 times in BNI Catty.
Approximately
1 crore 7655672 equity apps were bid for 4652000 equity apps.  The
IPO was subscribed 3.79 times due to bidding of Rs 3822 crore.
Almost let's
talk about the small NI category in this IPO.
So APO is subscribed for 3.72 times.  The
IPO was subscribed 3.72 times due to bidding of Rs 187374 crore.
Talking about the Retail Individual Investor category,
if you are applying in the Retail Individual Investor category in this IPO, then the
chances of allotment play here are quite high right now.  Because as of now the
IPO has not been fully oversubscribed in the retailers category.  The
IPO has been subscribed only for 0.82 times.  There is a
bidding of about 2899 crores and
in this IPO, the IPO is seen getting subscribed up to 2.83 times in the share holders category.
Still the chances of getting allotment here
are higher in Big NI category.  After that,
you people have a chance of getting allotment in Retailers Catery here and
then in Small NI Catery here.
If you are applying in Share Holders Category,
you can participate in maximum 13 lots here.
If you apply for 13 lots, then the
chance of getting allotment of one lot will
remain here.
Talking about the total number of times here,
after the end of the second day, the IPO has been
subscribed for 1.92 times.  Bids will be taken for
6 crore 73280 equity shares for 3 crore 50 lakh equity shares.
Due to the bid of 14575 crores, the IPO has almost doubled.
This IPO was subscribed for 0.73 times on the first day
and
after the end of the second day, it has been subscribed for 1.92 times,
which is a very good
response and till now 17 lakh applications have
come in this IPO. By tomorrow,
more than 50 lakh applications are expected here.
If the Kawaibi Catery IPO record
comes in this IPO, then you can see a rise again in the grey market
premium which has been falling
because
currently the grey market premium of this IPO is
seen trading at ₹29. If you add on ₹268 to ₹2165 here, then if we
talk about the listing price, then you can see approximately ₹24
coming out and there is a
chance of getting a listing on one lot of about 12%.
Here the IPO is seen listing at around ₹168 per
lot in the coming time.
Overall,
you will keep getting all the updates about this company from time to time.
Similarly, you
people have applied for this IPO today.   I am going to
apply tomorrow.   You
can tell us by commenting.  See you
in a new Infativa video.  Till then Jai
Hind, Jai